Menu

ExtLoans.com Privacy Policy
===========================

[Home](https://www.extloans.com/) » Privacy Policy

Effective Date: December 1, 2014

This Privacy Policy covers ExtLoans.com, its subsidiaries, and any of its websites ("Websites"). This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this Website and certain related services. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using, or submitting information, to this Website.

This Website is not intended for anyone under the age of eighteen (18) or persons residing outside of the United States. By accessing the Website on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, or other device (collectively, "Device"), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Policy, please do not use the Website.

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Website. We encourage you to periodically review our Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are using the information we collect.

**Collection of Information**

The main purpose of our Website ishelping you to find a loan from prospective lenders participating in ourdirect network of loan lenders ("participating lenders").

Personal Information

We collect personal information from you when you provide it to us, including by providing information to us to find you a loan, or when you contact us. This information may include, for example, name,date of birth, telephone number, mailing and home address, zip code, email address, social security number, bank account information, financial information, employment information, and driver's license number and state of issuance.

Non-Personal Information

When you visit the Website, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time of your visit, browser type, operating system, the specific web pages visited during your connection, and the domain name from which you accessed the Website. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Website, the areas or pages of the Website that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Website, the number of times you return to the Website and other clickstream data. We may also use non-personal information for statistical analysis, research, and other purposes.

Like many commercial websites, we analyze how visitors use our Site through what is known as "cookie" technology. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you access the Site and allows us to recognize you each time you visit the Site. We may use cookies to: (1) enhance or personalize your Website usage; (2) monitor Website usage; (3) manage the Website; and (4) improve the Website and our services. If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your computer by following your browser's help file directions. However, if your browser is set to reject cookies or you manually delete cookies, you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features that are currently on our Website, or that we may put on our Website in the future.

We may also use web beacons on the Website, in our emails and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your Site visit, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and/or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. We may also collect the URL of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Website. Web beacons help us analyze our Website visitors' behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Website and our advertising. We may work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyze this information.

We may combine the non-personal information we collect, such as through cookies and web beacons, with other information we have collected from you.

**Use of Information**

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your request for solicitation purposesand match you with a participating lender; (2) to respond to your inquiries; (3) to review Website usage and operations; (4) to address problems with the Website, our business or our services; (5) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business; (6) to monitor the Site for compliance with our Terms of Use and the law; (7) to enforce our contracts with you; and (8) to contact you with Website updates, newsletters and other informational and promotional materials from us and offers from participating lenders, as well as from other companies.

If you do not wish to receive communications from us about offers and promotions, you can opt-out of receiving these communications by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.extloans.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by following the instructions in the messages you receive.

**Disclosure of Information**

We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to facilitate your request by sharing your personal information to participating lenders so that they may contact you regarding a loan; (2) our related companies and service providers, to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (3)with consumer reporting and related agencies; (4) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Website Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (5) to respond to legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order) and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (6) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent. We may share aggregate, non-personal information about Website users with third parties.

**Credit Implications of Providing Your Personal Information**

Our participating third party lenders may verify, without limitation, your social security number and driver's license number, or any other qualifying identification and review your information against national databases to determine credit worthiness, standing and/or capacity. Please note that multiple inquiries on the three national databases (Equifax, Transunion and Experian) may result in a lowered credit score. By submitting your information you agree to allow third party providers to verify your information and check your credit as described in their policies and terms.

**Security**

We take reasonable and appropriate security precautions to secure the personal information that you choose to provide against the loss, misuse, alteration, or unauthorized access of such information. Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security or confidentiality of any personal information you transmit to us.

**Interest Based Advertising**

We may partner with ad networks and other ad serving providers ("Advertising Providers") who serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated sites. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information Advertising Providers collect about your visits to this site and elsewhere over time. Our Advertising Providers use cookies to personalize advertisements that you may see on other websites.

Because an industry-standard Do-Not-Track protocol has not yet been established, we will not change your browsing experience based on any "Do Not Track" signals that may be sent by certain browsers or selected by you.

However, you can visit www.cookiecentral.com and http://www.aboutads.info to learn more about this type of advertising and how to opt-out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") self-regulatory program. Note that electing to opt-out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice. As each browser is different, please check the help section of your browser for instructions on how to remove cookies and learn about other privacy and security settings that may be available.

**Children**

We do not direct the Website to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen.

**Third Party Websites**

The Website may contain links to third-party websites, including those for participating lenders, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for, nor do we endorse, any of the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any external site before disclosing any personal information. Please contact those websites directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide Personal Information to the Website may request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact our consumer support helpline at (888) 775-0859, via e-mail at [\[email protected\]](https://www.extloans.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or via regular mail at 1125 E Broadway, #545 Glendale, CA 91205

**Contact Us**

If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves your information, we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by calling (888) 775-0859. If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves your information, we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.

Select your state:
------------------

©2014-2021 ExtLoans.com

Menu

**Material Disclosure.** The operator of this website is not a lender, loan broker or agent for any lender or loan broker. We are an advertising referral service to qualified participating lenders that may be able to provide amounts between $100 and $1,000 for cash advance loans and up to $5000 for installment loans. Not all lenders can provide these amounts and there is no guarantee that you will be accepted by an independent, participating lender. This service does not constitute an offer or solicitation for loan products which are prohibited by any state law. This is not a solicitation for a particular loan and is not an offer to lend. We do not endorse or charge you for any service or product. Any compensation received is paid by participating lenders and only for advertising services provided. This service and offer are void where prohibited. We do not control and are not responsible for the actions of any lender. We do not have access to the full terms of your loan, including APR. For details, questions or concerns regarding your loan please contact your lender directly. Only your lender can provide you with information about your specific loan terms, their current rates and charges, renewal, payments and the implications for non-payment or skipped payments. The registration information submitted by you on this website will be shared with one or more participating lenders. You are under no obligation to use our service to initiate contact with a lender, apply for credit or any loan product, or accept a loan from a participating lender. Cash transfer times and repayment terms vary between lenders. Repayment terms may be regulated by state and local laws. Some faxing may be required. Be sure to review our FAQs for additional information on issues such as credit and late payment implications. These disclosures are provided to you for information purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. Use of this service is subject to this site’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

**Exclusions.** Residents of some states may not be eligible for some or all short-term, small-dollar loans. Residents of Arkansas, New York, Vermont and West Virginia are not eligible to use this website or service. The states serviced by this website may change from time to time, without notice.

**Credit Implications.** The operator of this website does not make any credit decisions. Independent, participating lenders that you might be connected with may perform credit checks with credit reporting bureaus or obtain consumer reports, typically through alternative providers to determine credit worthiness, credit standing and/or credit capacity. By submitting your information, you agree to allow participating lenders to verify your information and check your credit. Loans provided by independent, participating lenders in our network are designed to provide cash to you to be repaid within a short amount of time. The short-term loans are not a solution for long-term debt and credit difficulties. Only borrow an amount that can be repaid on the date of your next pay period. Consider seeking professional advice regarding your financial needs, risks and alternatives to short-term loans. Late Payments of loans may result in additional fees or collection activities, or both. Each lender has their own terms and conditions, please review their policies for further information. Nonpayment of credit could result in collection activities. Each lender has their own terms and conditions, please review their policies for further information. Every lender has its own renewal policy, which may differ from lender to lender. Please review your lender’s renewal policy.

**APR Disclosure.** Some states have laws limiting the Annual Percentage Rate (APR) that a lender can charge you. APRs for cash advance loans range from 200% and 1386%, and APRs for installment loans range from 6.63% to 225%. Loans from a state that has no limiting laws or loans from a bank not governed by state laws may have an even higher APR. The APR is the rate at which your loan accrues interest and is based upon the amount, cost and term of your loan, repayment amounts and timing of payments. Lenders are legally required to show you the APR and other terms of your loan before you execute a loan agreement. APR rates are subject to change.
